html5templatesdreamweaver.com 2013-08-05

# HTML5 Templates Dreamweaver Privacy Policy

####  What information do we collect? 

We collect information from you when you fill out a form. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

#### What do we use your information for? 

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

__To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

__To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

__To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

#### How do we protect your information? 

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

#### Do we use cookies? 

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. 

We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties? 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. 

#### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance 

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

#### Online Privacy Policy Only 

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

#### Your Consent 

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

#### Contacting Us 

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

__info[ @ ]html5templatesdreamweaver.com (close the spacings and remove the parenthesis)

This policy is powered by Free Privacy Policy and Rhino Support help desk software.
